<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sports on Webb Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sports on Webb Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Liverpool Goal Trends</title>
      <link>/2019/10/28/liverpool-scoring-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/10/28/liverpool-scoring-trends/</guid>
      <description>Looking into datahub’s Liverpool match data, I was able to investigate trends for goals scored by and against the Reds from 2009 up to last year’s EPL season. Boxplots below show this data over the ten year period.
 The number of goals are pretty variable, and with only 38 games per season, sample size is fairly low. I wanted to use Bayesian statistics to estimate goals for and against Liverpool based on these yearly samples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCAA March Madness - 2020</title>
      <link>/2019/09/17/ncaa-march-madness-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/09/17/ncaa-march-madness-2020/</guid>
      <description>Ah March… the birds are back (both motorized and natural), the weather is (a tiny bit) warmer, and 68 collegiate teams hash out their skills in an all-out, maddening basketball do-or-die nation-wide tournament. March is back baby!
I love NCAA March Madness. Although I never really watch college basketball through the regular season, I find the tournament too thrilling to ignore. Given that I have no understanding of most of the teams when the tourney starts, I have to rely on data and modeling techniques to make some sort of educated guesses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>